This morning, we still don't know what charges.
We don't know if there was even a warrant.
But two independent journalists and a BLM organizer were arrested at the direction of Pam Bondi.
This is not something that just happened overnight.
One of the reasons that I personally had to stop watching Late Night and CNN, NBC, all of them,
was when they were not reporting on a genocide, when they were firing reporter talking about
the war crimes that the Israeli government was committing.
We saw our government continue to supply bombs and weapons and support as the Israeli government
was assassinating journalist after journalist after journalist.
Not only did they arrest Don Lemon and Georgia Hood, but also TikTok kicked Bissan off of
the app and other Palestinian journalists yesterday.
I mean, we're right behind everything that we've done to Palestinians.
It's only a matter of time.
I don't know what the answer is to this.
I hope that other people have answers.
Personally, I think that if you're not already boycotting mainstream media, it's time to boycott
mainstream media for their complicity in capitulating to Trump.
If they did not report on Palestine, which none of them fucking did, they are equally responsible.
Don Lemon worked for CNN.
And he was like a golden child of CNN, along with Chris Cuomo just six years ago.
CNN should be saying something.
I think now is also a really important time.
If you're following content creators and journalists who report truthfully, and this is not even a
plug for myself.
This is whoever you follow and whoever you trust, go donate to them because a lot of people are doing
this for free without any funding.
I don't know.
Are there networks in place for independent journalists and content creators to have access
to attorneys to make sure that they have safety mechanisms in place?
I have no idea.
I just know that we know where this is going because we just fucking saw it happen in Palestine.